John Rubio

Portfolio: <u>livelifedev.github.io</u> GitHub: <u>github.com/livelifedev</u>

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/john-m-rubio

Sydney - 0424 505 157 - johnrubio93@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Animation graduate and career changer into tech, with a focus on full stack web development. Strong visual, technical and problem-solving background having studied visual effects and 3D animation. Proficient communication skills with work experience in customer-oriented roles.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Node
- Express

- React
- Redux
- Ruby / Rails
- 2D and 3D design
- Git

EDUCATION

Diploma of IT in Web Development

Coder Academy (February 2019 – Present)

Front End Web Development Track

Team Treehouse (November 2018 – January 2019)

Bachelor of Interactive Media in VFX & Animation

SAE Creative Media Institute (February 2012 – February 2015)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Rensa Health (September 2019 – Present)

Responsibilities:

- Build features required for main product in React
- Build UI from wireframes and mockups

Frontend Developer (Intern)

SafetyCulture (August 2019 – September 2019)

Responsibilities:

- Participate in Agile workflow as a member of the engineering team
- Fix bugs and improve UI of the main product in React
- Test and deploy to sandbox and to production
- Document and report any bugs found in the main product

Shop Assistant/Weekend Supervisor

Neutral Bay Vinnies (November 2015 – April 2018)

Responsibilities:

- Responsible for opening and closing store
- Managed till and cash flow
- Supervised volunteers and newer staff members
- Managed stock in store front and back

Backpacker Hostel Staff

Various backpacker hostels (April 2016 – July 2017)

Responsibilities:

- Welcomed and checked-in guests
- Provided help and information to guests
- Organised hostel activities

Promotion & Sales Rep

Australian Sales and Promotions (February 2015 – October 2015)

Responsibilities:

- Actively engaged with potential customers to promote and sell product
- Listened to customer problems and provided them solution through product
- Provided a great customer experience to leave customer feeling satisfied